https://www.dayspring.com/about/terms-of-use-privacy-policy#dns

Close Menu
ChristmasNew ArrivalsCardsMenuClose Menu
Encourage Hearts with beautiful Christmas Cards!
CardsView All CardsBirthdayAnniversaryWeddingEncouragementPraying for You - Difficult TimesThank You & AppreciationThinking of YouSympathyGet WellAll Occasion & BlankBaby CelebrationsCongratulationsFriendshipChurch Occasions & CelebrationsCard FormatsCard CollectionsAll Seasons
New Arrivals
Best Sellers
Staff Favorites
HelpSign In
Gifts & HomeMenuClose Menu
Our Favorite Gifts Sale - Up to 50% Off Select Gifts for Christmas!
Gifts & HomeView All Gifts & HomeNew Arrivals2020-2021 Agenda PlannersCalendars & PlannersJewelryApparelTotes, Bags & AccessoriesGift SetsMugs & DrinkwareBaby Gifts & Clothing365 Day Perpetual CalendarsGifts for KidsKJV GiftsWillow TreeGift BagsStationery(in)courageHomeOccasions
New Arrivals
Hope for Today
Candace Cameron Bure Collection
HelpSign In
Books & BiblesMenuClose Menu
New Releases Available Now!
Books & BiblesView All Books & BiblesBooksBiblesDevotionalsGift BooksJournals and NotebooksPrayers To ShareChildren's BooksBible CoversBible JournalingBooks Coming Soon
New Arrivals
Best Sellers
Books Coming Soon
HelpSign InSaleMenuClose Menu
Our Favorite Gifts Sale - Up to 50% Off Select Gifts for Christmas!
SaleView All SaleOur Favorite Gifts SaleClearanceBuy in BulkHelpSign In eCard Studio
Menu
Close Menu
Fall Ecards
eCards
View All eCards
COVID-19
Christmas (December 25th)
Winter
Birthday
Encouragement
Friendship
Praying for You
Thank You
Shareable Scripture
Get Well
Terms of Use/Privacy
Job Openings (EOE)
Store Locator
Supplier Code of Conduct
Help
Sign In
Help
Menu
Close Menu
Help
Sign In
Enjoy Free U.S. Standard Shipping On Every Order Through December 11th with Code FREESHIP
Start Here
Enjoy Free U.S. Standard Shipping On Every OrderThrough December 11th with Code FREESHIP
Start Here
Details
Privacy Policy
DaySpring is a wholly owned subsidiary of Hallmark, Inc.
At DaySpring, we strive to help people create a caring and more connected world. Through our cards, products and services, we help people connect and enrich lives.
To do this, we use the information you’ve provided to us through your interactions with DaySpring, as well as the purchases you’ve made with us. This helps us create a more tailored experience just for you, helps us deliver coupons and offers, and helps us show you marketing that showcases the products and services we think you’d enjoy.
Hallmark and its subsidiaries currently do not, nor have we in the past, received any money from third party companies in exchange for your personal information. Any information we share with others is to help provide you a quick and easy shopping experience and is not allowed to be shared with anyone else.
We treasure the special relationship we have with you and strive to maintain the trust you give us. If you’re still curious about what type of information DaySpring uses to create your specialized shopping experience, please continue by reading the full policy below.
Our privacy policy is reviewed regularly to make sure we continue to serve your privacy interests. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on our website. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our digital properties and will replace any prior policies.
Account Information
Information We Collect
How We Use Your Information
California Consumer Privacy Act
Right to Know
Right to Delete
Do Not Sell
Other California Privacy Rights
Nevada Consumer Opt-Out Requests
Personalized Messages
How to contact us
Account Information
How do I access and change my email contact preferences?
If you do not want to be contacted by DaySpring for promotional purposes, you may change your preferences at any time. First, make sure you are signed in to your DaySpring.com account. Then navigate to “Newsletter Subscriptions” from the “My Account” section of the site. You may choose which email communications you wish to no longer receive.
How do I access and change my personal information?
You can change or delete your personal information anytime. Sign in to your DaySpring.com account. You can update any of your personal information by choosing what information you would like to update. Navigate to the “My Account” section of the site to update your name, email, primary mailing address or password. You can also update shipping addresses and saved payment methods.
Information We Collect
See how your information and your privacy help make up your DaySpring experience. At DaySpring, your information is used to create an easy and enjoyable shopping experience for you.
The information you provide to us is used to help create a more tailored experience to help you find products and experiences that we think you’d be interested in. This information is given to us when you create an account with any of our programs or services and when you shop with us. There are several ways we may collect information from you.
Information you provide directly to us:
Name
Email address
Mailing address
Shipping addresses
Phone number
Date of birth
Account information, including any information used for future loyalty programs
Messages and photographs provided by you for personalized cards and gifts
Information provided by you as you interact with the Customer Care team
Information provided by you as you provide feedback on products or services offered on our sites and apps
Information relating to transactions and products purchased, including payment information, billing address and purchase, return and exchange information
Information collected passively:
Device information, including device model, operating system version, device date and time, unique device identifiers, mobile network information
Geolocation of your device
How you use our sites and mobile applications, including search terms and pages you visit
Information from third parties:
Information we receive from business partners, including online advertising networks.
Social media platforms, including Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Pinterest and Instagram.
How We Use Your Information
At DaySpring, we are committed to the security and privacy of your information.
When you provide us with information about yourself, we only share that information with our partners, like the businesses which help process your orders, service providers (like delivery companies), and contractors. We give them this information to help fulfill your orders, offer you products and services, and other consumer service-based needs. Likewise, these companies provide information to us so we can provide you with product or service suggestions we think you might be interested in.
DaySpring allows certain companies to place tracking technologies like cookies and pixels on our sites, which allow these companies to receive information about your activity on our websites. Those companies may use that data to show you more relevant advertisements and promotions. Learn more about your ability to control privacy settings at the companies we work with, which include but are not limited to, Facebook/Instagram, Evergage, LiveRamp, Pinterest, Sailthru and Google/YouTube.
You always have control over whether these technologies work on your devices. You can disable them entirely by opting-out of third-party cookies or using your mobile device ID for targeted advertising. You can also use preferences or settings on your device(s) to manage your privacy controls.
Any non-DaySpring company we work with is contractually not allowed to use this information in any other way. We value the trust you place in us, and this is one way we strive to preserve it.
Security
To protect your information, we use the same technology your bank uses to protect your information. For added security, we also use a digital secure server ID to protect you when you use our sites.
In other words, the parties to whom we provide your information are people that help us help you. And we require them to join us in keeping your information safe.
While we are careful with how your information is treated and are selective when choosing other companies and websites with which we interact, any site DaySpring links to is out of our control. So when interacting with sites outside of DaySpring, please make sure to read their Privacy Policy before sharing your information with them.
California Consumer Privacy Act
Effective January 1, 2020, if you are a California resident, you have expanded rights regarding the collection and disclosure of information about yourself as part of the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA).
Only you or your authorized representative may make these requests. You may make requests for data disclosure or portability no more than twice in a 12-month period. In your request, you must provide enough information to allow us to verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information, or their authorized representative. You must also describe your request with enough detail so that we can understand, evaluate and respond to it. We can’t respond to your request if we can’t verify your identity. Making such a request does not require you to create an account with us, and we will only use the information you provide in a request to verify your identity. Authorized representatives must provide a signed, written permission to make such requests or power of attorney. You may also make a request on behalf of your minor child.
If you have questions about any of these rights, please call us at 1-877-203-5515.
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights.
Information We Collect
Below are the categories and examples of information we collect, along with how we use that information. Unless otherwise noted, we collect this information from our users, customers and service providers. Unless otherwise noted, we use this information to enable use of our sites, services and products; to communicate with you; to understand how users interact with our site; and to improve our products and services. Unless otherwise noted, we may share this information with our service providers.
• Identifiers such as name, mailing address, IP address, email address or account name. We may generate these identifiers internally, such as a loyalty or customer number.
• Personal information categories such as name, signature, address or phone number. (Information in this category may overlap with other categories.)
• Protected classification characteristics including age, gender, race, ethnicity, religion, marital status, and veteran/military status.
• Internet/network activity, such as browsing history, search history, banners you click, and pages you visit on our site.
• Commercial information such as what you purchase or consider purchasing from us and other requests you make. This information allows us to complete those transactions and deliver your orders in a timely manner.
• Geolocation data, such as the location of your computer or mobile device. This helps us show you the nearest stores to your location.
• Sensory data such as audio, electronic, visual or similar information.
• Inferences drawn from other personal information may be generated internally. These inferences may include preferences, characteristics, predispositions and behaviors, and are used to help us provide you more relevant products and services and provide a better experience on our website and apps. We do not share this information.
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use it in materially different purposes without providing you notice. Your personal information may be shared with third parties for business purpose (“service providers”). Service providers are required to keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose other than what is specified in what is outlined in our contract with them.
Right to Know
In accordance with the CCPA, you have the right to know what information we have collected about you. You can request us to disclose this personal information no more than twice in a 12-month period. This information will be provided in an accessible format that allows you to transmit your data from one entity to another.
If you would like a list of the information we maintain, we will email it to you within 45 days of your request. If we require more time (up to 90 days) we’ll let you know this, and the reason why, in writing. Contact our Customer Care department at DaySpringPrivacy@Hallmark.com or call 1-877-203-5515 to proceed with this request.
Right to Delete
In accordance with the CCPA, you have the right to request that we delete the information we have about you. DaySpring offers several services that require certain information in order to work. Deleting your information can affect your ability to:
• Earn exclusive offers and coupons
• Access services like DaySpring eCards
• Get the inside scoop on the exciting new surprises DaySpring is working on
• Have a quicker check-out experience on DaySpring.com
We will attempt to complete your request within 45 days. If we require more time (up to 90 days) we’ll let you know this, and the reason why, in writing. To proceed, contact our Customer Care department at DaySpringPrivacy@Hallmark.com or call 1-877-203-5515 to provide the information we need to validate your request.
Do Not Sell
In accordance with the CCPA, if you are 16 years or older, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information. Consumers who we know are under 16 are already opted-out of this sale of information, unless they have specifically exercised their right to opt-in. A parent or guardian must provide an opt-in for consumers less than 13.
DaySpring does not now, nor have we in the past, sell consumer information to third parties for financial gain. What we sometimes do is to track your device by sending non-identifying information to partners, who then use it to provide you relevant marketing messages. When we do this, your personal information (name, phone number, etc.) is not shared with them.
Under the CCPA, sharing data for online advertising like this may be considered a “sale” of information, and we are required to allow you to opt out of selling your information. To help you manage the tracking of your information, including browsing history and targeted marketing efforts, you can take action by opting out of cookies and device ID tracking. Please read the “How We Use Your Information” section of the policy for more information on how you can manage your privacy via third parties. You can also manage privacy options directly in your device preferences or settings.
Other California Privacy Rights
California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as S.B. 27) allows customers to opt out of having your personal information shared for direct marketing purposes. To make this request, you may write us at DaySpring Cards Consumer Care; P.O. Box 1010; Siloam Springs, AR 72761; or call 1-877-203-5515. Within 30 days of receiving your request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding year, along with the names and addresses of those third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted to locations other than those specified above.
Nevada Consumer Opt-Out Requests
Nevada S.B. 220 provides consumers with the ability to opt out of the sale of their personal information. We do not sell your personal information as defined in S.B. 220. However, should our practices change in the future and you wish to opt out, your request must be submitted to DaySpringPrivacy@Hallmark.com. We will record your request and avoid selling your information at any point in the future.
Personalized Messages
Your ecards and personalized greeting card messages are kept confidential and secure. Ecards will only be accessed when it is necessary to complete your order. For order fulfillment, a representative may view your message. Once again, third parties are not allowed to use this information. They can only fulfill orders and help with your questions.  We do reserve the right to work with law enforcement officials in the investigation of possible unlawful activities of our customers related to communications made on our site. We will have no legal responsibility for such disclosures.
How to Contact Us
You may contact us our Customer Care department by email at webcare@dayspring.com, or call us at 1-877-751-4347. The information you provide is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file your comments and share them with our customer care team to improve our service in the future.
If you still have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please write us at: DaySpring Cards Consumer CareP.O. Box 1010Siloam Springs, AR 72761
ArticlesAboutAbout DayspringMinistry of CardsOur Mission and ValuesPrivacy PolicySupplier Code of ConductCA Privacy NoticeContact UsFind a StoreShipping InformationJob Openings (EOE)Affiliate ProgramFrequently Asked QuestionsLove Over All
Inbox Inspiration
Our very latest products, content & ideas.
THANK YOU.
Your first email is on the way.
* PLEASE ENTER A VALID EMAIL ADDRESS
Shop
New Arrivals
Best Sellers
Our Favorites
Gifts for Her
New Cards
About
About DaySpring
Ministry of Cards
Our Mission and Values
Privacy Policy
CA Privacy Notice
CA Do Not Sell
Job Openings (EOE)
Store Locator
Connect
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Instagram
#LiveYourFaith
Help
Mon-Fri
© 2020 DaySpring Cards, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Promotion Details
To redeem $20 off any $60 purchase, enter promo code GREENMONDAY in cart. Offer not valid on Willow Tree Collection. Offer valid Monday, December 10, 2018 at 12:01am CT through Tuesday, December 11, 2018 at 11:59pm CT. Limit one promo code per order. Offer cannot be applied to previous purchases and cannot be redeemed for cash. Terms are subject to change.
Therefore encourage one another
and build each other up as you are already doing.
1 Thess 5:11 CSB
